<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cinema Era</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="title_activity_view_all__film">View_all_Film</string>
    <string name="server_api_url">http://cinemaera.lalpun.com.np/ERA/api/</string>
    <string name="Image_url">http://cinemaera.lalpun.com.np/ERA/MoviesPoster/</string>
    <string name="Trailer_Video_url">http://cinemaera.lalpun.com.np/ERA/Trailer_vedios/</string>
    <string name="Full_movie_url">http://cinemaera.lalpun.com.np/ERA/Full_movies/</string>

<!--    <string name="server_api_url">http://192.168.100.129:8888/ERA/api/</string>-->
<!--    <string name="Image_url">http://192.168.100.129:8888/ERA/MoviesPoster/</string>-->
<!--    <string name="Trailer_Video_url">http://192.168.100.129:8888/ERA/Trailer_vedios/</string>-->
<!--    <string name="Full_movie_url">http://192.168.100.129:8888/ERA/Full_movies/</string>-->
    <string name="PrivacyPolicy">This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which "Cinema Era" collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each user) of "Cinema Era" Mobile application. This
        privacy policy applies to the Apps and all products and services offered by "Cinema Era" \n\nBy using this App you accept this policy. If you do not agree with it, please do not use our this App. If you choose to use
        my service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The personal information that i collect is used for providing and improving the service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
        \n\nInformation Collection and Use:\n\nFor a better experience, while using our service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information.\n\nThis app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.\n\nLink to privacy policy
        of third party service providers used by this app is Khalti Payment.\n\nSecurity:\n\nI value your trust in providing us your personal information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it.But remember that no method of transmission over the internet or method
        of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and i cannot guarantee its absolute security.\n\nLink to other sites:\n\nThis service may contain links to other sites.if you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me.
        Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the privacy policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites or services.\n\nChanges to this privacy policy:\n\nI may update our privacy policy from time
        to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new privacy policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.\n\nContact us:\n\nIf you have any questions or suggestions about my privacy policy,
        don not hesitate to contact me.</string>
</resources>
